// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Comment dit-on 'où' en anglais ?",
    answer: "Where",
    options: [
      "Where",
      "How",
      "What",
      "Whose"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Comment dit-on 'quand' en anglais ?",
    answer: "When",
    options: [
      "How long",
      "Why",
      "When",
      "Who"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Comment dit-on 'pourquoi' en anglais ?",
    answer: "Why",
    options: [
      "How long",
      "What",
      "Whose",
      "Why"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Comment dit-on 'comment' en anglais ?",
    answer: "How",
    options: [
      "When",
      "Where",
      "How",
      "Who"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Comment dit-on 'qui' en anglais ?",
    answer: "Who",
    options: [
      "How old",
      "Who",
      "Where",
      "How long"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Comment dit-on 'à qui' en anglais ?",
    answer: "Whose",
    options: [
      "Whose",
      "How",
      "How long",
      "When"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Comment dit-on 'que, quel' en anglais ?",
    answer: "What",
    options: [
      "Who",
      "Why",
      "Whose",
      "What"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Comment dit-on 'lequel' en anglais ?",
    answer: "Which",
    options: [
      "How old",
      "Which",
      "Whose",
      "Where"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Pour parler de l'âge de quelqu'un on dit ?",
    answer: "How old",
    options: [
      "How old",
      "What",
      "Which",
      "Why"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Pour parler d'une durée on dit ?",
    answer: "How long",
    options: [
      "How",
      "How old",
      "Whose",
      "How long"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];